Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 6. Public Relations and Media Files, 1972-2010 TJU.2010.01.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Media Appearances, 1972-2010; II.
  - Action News: Issues and Answers, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 15)
  - Celebrity Softball Game, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 16)
  - CNN: Evans and Novak; CNN: Larry King Live, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 17)
  - Fox 5 DC Morning News: FBI Agent Earl Edwin Pitt's Arrest for Espionage; Business Insiders; NAHB Builders Show, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 18)
  - Fox Morning News: Interview about Freeman; Good Morning America Segment: FBI Files; Pennsylvania Cable Network: Bellefonete & Lewistown Town Meetings, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 19)
  - Fox Morning News: Interview with Specter on Terrorism; CNBC: Interview with Specter on Terrorism, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 20)
  - Fox Morning News: Specter Interview; Fox News Center; CNN: Late Edition; Biz Insider; Celebrity Softball Game, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 21)
  - Job Corps 30th Anniversary Congressional Tributes, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 22)
  - Local Channel 7 News: White House for Sale, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 23)
  - NAHB Builders Show, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 24)
  - Report on Khobar Towers and Intelligence Funding; Judiciary Committee: Oversight Hearings with Questions and Answers; CNBC: Flat Tax and Presidential; Judiciary Committee; C-SPAN 2 Cable: New Hampshire Republican Forum, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 25)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing Regarding FBI Files: White House Access to FBI Background Summaries, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 26)
  - Why Can't I Be President?, 1996 (Box 1123, Video 27)
  - Senator Arlen Specter Interview: Gulf War Syndrome, January 8, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 28)
  - NET Direct Line with Paul Weyrich: Reaction to the Inaugural Address, January 20, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 29)
  - Weyrich Show: Reaction to Inaugural, January 20, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 30)
  - The State of the Union, January 27, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 31)
  - CNN Headline News: Clips of Ebonics Hearing, January 28, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 32)
  - CNN: Clips on Veteran's Committee Hearing with General Norman Schwarzkopf; VA Gulf War Syndrome, January 29, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 33)
  - Committee on Veteran's Affairs: Gulf War Syndrome with General Schwarzkopf, January 29, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 34-35)
  - Floor Statement: Madeleine Albright Nomination, January 29, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 36-37)
  - Floor Statement: The Case for Energy Conservation, January 30, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 38)
  - This is America with Dennis Wholey: Show #273, Guests: Specter, Ferraro, Graves, Roberts, Margolies-Mezvinsky, Brown, January 31, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 39)
  - Fox News Sunday: Campaign Finance Opposite Senator Levin, February 2, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 40)
  - Philadelphia Local Coverage: Senator Specter, Gulf War Syndrome, February 3, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 41)
  - Floor Statement: Mammogram, February 4, 1997 (Box 1123, Video 42)
  - Floor Statements: Mammogram, February 4, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 1)
  - Random Network Coverage: State of the Union Address, February 4, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 2)
  - Senator Specter's Reaction to State of the Union, February 4 and 5, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 3)
  - C-SPAN: Coverage of Breast Cancer Hearing, February 5, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 4)
  - Floor Statements: Case for Energy Conservation, February 5, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 5-6)
  - Subcommittee on Labor, HHS, Education; Mammogram Hearing, February 5, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 7)
  - Floor Statement: Tribute to Pamela Harriman, February 6, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 8-9)
  - Drug Treatment Program, February 7, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 10)
  - Gulf War Syndrome, February 7, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 11)
  - PSA, February 10, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 12-13)
  - reuters Financial Television: Interview on the Federal Budget, February 11, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 14)
  - Floor Statement: Dairy Resolution (passed), February 13, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 15)
  - Floor Statement: Anthony Lake, February 14, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 16)
  - Floor Statement: Dairy Resolution, February 14, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 17-18)
  - Senator Specter Meeting with Disabled, February 17, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 19)
  - CNN, CBS News: Senator Specter's Comments on Ken Starr and His Decision to Stay on as Independent Counsel, February 21, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 20)
  - MSNBC News: Interview with Senator Specter on Ken Starr's Decision to Stay On as Independent Counsel, February 21, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 21-22)
  - Fox News Sunday: Interview with Senator Specter About Ken Starr's Decision to Stay On as Independent Counsel, February 23, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 23)
  - Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, and Harrisburg Coverage: Senator Arlen Specter, February 21-24, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 24)
  - CNBC The Charles Grodin Show: Interview with Senators Specter and McCain on Campaign Finance, February 26, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 25)
  - CNN Interview with Senator Specter on Campaign Finance, February 26, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 26)
  - CNN: News Segment Fundraising Investigation, February 26, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 27)
  - CNN Interview: Gulf War, February 27, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 28)
  - CNN Interview with Senator Specter about Khamisiyah (News Conference 4:30-5:30 p.m.), February 27, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 29-30)
  - CNN Interview with Senators Kerry and Specter on Campaign Finance, February 28, 1997 (Box 1124, Video 31)
  - The Case for Energy Conservation; Mammogram, February 1997 (Box 1124, Video 32)
  - Senator Specter: Mammography Awareness, March 3, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 1)
  - News Coverage In State, February 21-24, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 2)
  - BBC Interview with Senator Specter on Gulf War, March 5, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 3-4)
  - Washington Hotline, March 5, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 5-6)
  - CNBC Charles Grodin Show: Campaign Finance with McCain, March 6, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 7)
  - Senator Specter, March 7, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 8)
  - Floor Statement: Campaign Finance Investigation, March 11, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 9)
  - Floor Statement: Government Affairs Scope, March 11, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 10)
  - Pamela Harriman Statement; Dairy Resolution (passed); Dairy Resolution; Anthony Lake; Tribute to Pamela Harriman; Anthony Lake; Government Affairs Scope, March 11, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 11)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Campaign Contribution, March 11, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 12)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Interview with Senators Specter and Lieberman on Campaign Finance; Floor Statement: Louis Freeh, Abstinenec, Intro Children's Health Bill, Mammograms, March 13, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 13-17)
  - Conrail Merger, March 14, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 18)
  - Floor Statement: Campaign Finance, Shooting in Israel, Arafat's Meeting excluding Israel, Independent Counsel for Campaign Finance, March 14, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 19)
  - Campaign Finance Investigation; Character Counts, FBI Criticism, Intro Healthy Children; Character; Campaign Finance, Shooting in Israel, March 13 and 14, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 20)
  - ABC This Week: Interview with Senators Specter and Kerry on Chinese Money and Campaign Finance, March 16, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 21)
  - This Week: Specter and Kerry Campaign Finance, March 16, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 22)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Enterprise Zones, March 17, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 23)
  - CNBC: Interview with Senators Specter and Kerry on Campaign Finance; Also on Tape: Daschle Briefing, March 18, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 24)
  - Floor Statement: Campaign Finance Amendment, March 18, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 25)
  - Specter/Hollings: Press Conference Campaign Finance, March 18, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 26)
  - Floor Statement: Merrick Garland, DC Court of APpeals, Judicial Nomination Process, March 19, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 27)
  - C-SPAN: Story on Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, Hearing on Conrail Merger, March 20, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 28)
  - CSX/Conrail Merger Senate Transportation Subcommittee, March 20, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 29)
  - Capitol Insight, March 21, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 30-31)
  - C-SPAN Speech on Law Library at Supreme Court, March 22, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 32)
  - WGAL, WHP, WHTM News Segments: Tape 12 Conrail, March 24, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 33)
  - Senator Arlen Specter Meets Dairy Farmers, March 25, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 34)
  - NBC News/CNN McVeigh: Death Penalty/Hearing in LA, March 26, 1997 (Box 1125, Video 35)
  - NBC Nightly News: Mammograms, March 26, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 1-2)
  - News Appearances: Dairy and Mammograms In State, March 25 and 31, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 3)
  - Senator Specter/Mammography Unit, March 31, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 4)
  - Government Affairs Committee: Investigation of Campaign Finance, March 1997 (Box 1126, Video 5)
  - Hearing on Conrail Merger; Senator Specter/Funding for Beltway; Interview with Senator Specter on Mammograms; McLaughlin Group One on One; Interview with Senator Specter on Peru; Interview with Senators Specter and Durbin on Reno and Independent Counsel, March 1997 (Box 1126, Video 6)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Conrail Jobs, March 1997 (Box 1126, Video 7)
  - Senator Specter Holds Hearing on Conrail Jobs, April 7, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 8)
  - Conrail News Stories From State Tape 15, April 11, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 9)
  - McLaughlin Group One on One: Interview with Senator Specter and Hanan Aswari on Palestinian Issues, April 14, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 10-11)
  - BLDG and Construction Trades National Conference, April 15, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 12)
  - PSA; Washington Hotline Live, April 15, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 13)
  - PSAs, April 15, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 14-16)
  - Washington Hotline, April 15, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 17-18)
  - Floor Statement: Flat Tax Bill, April 16, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 19-20)
  - Judiciary Committee: Victim's Rights, April 16, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 21)
  - Subcommittee on Labor, HHS, Education: Mammogram Hearing; Judiciary Committee: Victim's Rights, February 5 and April 16, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 22)
  - Campaign Finance Amendment; Merrick Garland, DC Court of Appeals; Flat Tax Bill; Dairy Priecs, April 17, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 23)
  - CNN Report on Veteran's Hearing with Colin Powell, April 17, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 24-25)
  - Floor Statement: Dairy Prices, April 17, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 26)
  - Senator Specter: Flat Tax/Chemical Weapons, April 17, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 27)
  - Labor Hearing Segments: Children's Health, April 18, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 28)
  - State Coverage: Flat Tax/Chemical Weapons segments, April 17, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 29)
  - Floor Statement: Chemical Weapons Convention, April 23, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 30-31)
  - WHTM TV News Conference: Chemical Weapons, April 24, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 32)
  - CNBC: Interview with Senator Specter on Peru, April 24, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 33)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Chemical Weapons, April 24, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 34)
  - Floor Statement: Chemical Weapons Convention, April 25, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 35)
  - Senator Arlen Specter, April 27 and 28, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 36)
  - Floor Statement: Anthony Lake, April 29, 1997 (Box 1126, Video 37)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Defense Distribution Regional Site Cutback, April 29, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 1)
  - CNN Crossfire: Attorney General Reno's Testimony, April 30, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 2)
  - CNN Crossfire: Interview with Senators Specter and Durbin on Reno and Independent Counsel, April 30, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 3)
  - Committee on Judiciary: Attorney General Reno's Testimony, April 30, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 4-5)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Democratic Fundraising, April 30, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 6)
  - Chemical Weapons Convention; Interview with Senators Kerry and Specter on Campaign Finance, April 1997 (Box 1127, Video 7)
  - Conrail Dairy Farmers, April 1997 (Box 1127, Video 8)
  - Pittsburgh Airport Improvement, May 5, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 9)
  - Senator Arlen Specter: Milk Prices, May 1-6, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 10-11)
  - CNN Coverage of LHHS Hearing on the 25th Anniversary of the War on Cancer (Sam Donaldson and Arnold Palmer), May 7, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 12)
  - State Coverage: Pittsburgh Airport Improvement, May 8, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 13)
  - Washington Hotline (Live), May 8, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 14-15)
  - Full Appropriations Committee: Sexual Harassment in the VA, May 13, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 16-17)
  - News Segments: Milk Prices, May 1 and 6, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 18)
  - Transit Awareness Week: Senator Specter, May 12-13, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 19-20)
  - Senator Arlen Specter at Meadville High School, May 16, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 21-22)
  - Senator Arlen Specter in Erie, May 17, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 23)
  - Senator Specter Pushing for Funding for Locks, May 20, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 24)
  - Capitol Insight, May 22, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 25)
  - Satellite Feed: Acceptance Speech to Pennsylvania Partners, May 22, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 26-27)
  - Labor Secretary Visit: Senator Specter, May 27, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 28)
  - Pennsylvania Cable Network Profile on Senator specter, May 1997 (Box 1127, Video 29)
  - News Compilation: Senator Arlen Specter, June 2, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 30)
  - Committee on Judiciary: Louis Freeh Testimony on FBI Oversight and Tenet, Reno, June 4, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 31-34)
  - Appropriations Hearing with Christopher Reeve, June 5, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 35-36)
  - Celebrities War on Cancer Sen. Support, June 5, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 37)
  - CNN Coverage of LHHS Hearing with Christopher Reeve and Report of VA Benefits Legislation, June 5, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 38)
  - Hearing for Spinal Cord Research, June 5, 1997 (Box 1127, Video 39)
  - Appropriations Hearing with Christopher Reeve, June 5, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 1)
  - Senator Specter Discusses Military Scandal; Senator Specter/Toby Hanna, June 6, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 2)
  - Visit to Scranton/Wilkes-Barre, June 6, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 3)
  - Tax Break for Historic Preservation, June 9, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 4)
  - WCAU-TV Philadelphia, June 9, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 5)
  - NBC Nightly News: Interview with Senator Specter on McVeigh Death Penalty (1994 Crime Bill), June 11, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 6)
  - Committee on Judiciary: Eric Holder, June 13, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 7)
  - Senator Specter: Illegal Contributions, June 13-14, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 8)
  - Sat Feed B-Roll: Cheese Steaks, June 13, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 9)
  - WPXI, KYW, WGAL, WCAU, WHTM: Illegal Contribution, FEC Report, June 13-14, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 10)
  - WPHL, WTXF: Senator Specter Terrorism Conference, June 16, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 11-12)
  - Ira Einhorn Case: Senator Arlen Specter, June 17, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 13)
  - Floor Statement: Palestinian Aid (Amendment to State Department Authorization), June 18, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 14)
  - Specter-Torricelli Veterans Bill, Abstinance/Abortion Statement, Commemoration of Indian Independence Day, June 18, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 15)
  - McVeigh out of Military Cemetery, May 18 - June 19, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 16)
  - Floor Statements: ADAPT, TWA, African-American music, June 20, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 17)
  - Conrail/Airport Busway/TWA Victims, June 23-24, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 18)
  - WPVI-TV Channel 6 Philadelphia: Ira Einhorn News Coverage, June 23, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 19)
  - News Coverage: McVeigh Veteran Benefits, June 23, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 20)
  - Senator Specter: Airport Busway, June 23, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 21)
  - WTAE News: Airport Busway, June 23, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 22)
  - Arlen Specter, June 26, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 23)
  - Capitol Insight with Jim Nichols, June 26, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 24)
  - Committee on Judiciary Hearing: Tobacco Settlement, June 27, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 25-26)
  - Various Network Coverage: Federal Budget and Governmental Affairs Committee Meeting, June 27, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 27)
  - NBC Meet the Press: Interview with Senators Specter and Glenn on Government Affairs Hearings on Campaign Finance Abuses, July 6, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 28)
  - The 700 Club/CBS News: Campaign Finance Hearings, July 8, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 29)
  - News 10 WCAU-TV NBC Philadelphia: Campaign Finance, July 8, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 30)
  - Christian Broadcasting Network 700 Club: Interview with Senator Specter about Campaign Finance and Governmental Affairs Hearings, July 8, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 31)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Interview with Senator Specter about Campaign Finance Hearings, July 8, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 32-33)
  - Government Affairs Committee Hearing: Campaign Finance Reform, July 8, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 34-36)
  - PBS NewsHour with Jim Lehrer: Interview with Senators Specter and Glenn about Governmental Affairs Hearings, July 8, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 37-38)
  - CNBC Hardball with Chris Matthews: Interview with Senator Specter on Campaign Finance Abuses, July 9, 1997 (Box 1128, Video 39)
  - CNN Crossfire: Interview with Senators Specter and Durbin about Campaign Finance and Governmental Affairs Hearings, July 9, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 1)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee Hearing: Richard Sullivan (witness), July 9, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 2-3)
  - CNBC Hardball with Chris Matthews, July 9, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 4)
  - MSNBC: Interview with Senators Specter and Torricelli on Campaign Finance Abuses, July 9, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 5)
  - Sununu v. Press Guests: Senator Arlen Specter/Senator Richard Durbin, July 9, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 6)
  - Money Trial; Crossfire; Hardball, July 8 and 9, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 7)
  - CNN Crossfire with Senator Durbin: Campaign Finance, July 10, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 8)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee Hearing: Richard Sullivan (witness), July 10, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 9-10)
  - Judiciary Bork Hearing, July 10, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 11)
  - MSNBC with Senator Torricelli: Government Affairs Hearing, July 10, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 12)
  - WTFX, WPHL News Coverage: Constitution Center, Welfare Reform, Campaign Finance, July 1 and 6, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 13)
  - Satellite Interview: National Association of Student Financial Aid Advisors, July 11, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 14-15)
  - BLDG and Construction Trades: National Conference; Various: AS at Meadville High School; Capitol Insight; Satellite Feed: Acceptance Speech to PA Partners; Satellite Interview: Nation Association of Student Financial Aid Advisors, July 15, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 16)
  - CBS Face the Nation: Interview with Senators Specter, Lieberman, Collins, Nickles and Levin on Campaign Finance Abuses, July 13, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 17-18)
  - Fox News Sunday, NBC Meet the Press: Campaign Finance Abuses, July 13, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 19)
  - Campaign Finance, July 10-15, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 20)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee Hearing, July 15-17, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 21-26)
  - Direct Line with Paul Weyrich: Campaign Finance Hearings, July 17, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 27-28)
  - African Elephant Hunts Funded, July 21, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 29)
  - Teen and Tobacco ADA Funding, July 22, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 30)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee Hearing: Benton Becker, Michael Baroody, July 23, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 31-32)
  - Governmental Affairs: Benton Becker and Michael Baroody; Floor Statements: LIHEAP, July 23, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 33)
  - Various News Segments, July 23, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 34)
  - Floor Statement: Independent Counsel for Campaign Finance, July 24, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 35)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee Hearing: Fred Volcansek, Haley Barbour, July 24, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 36-37)
  - Governmental Affairs: Fred Volcansek and Haley Barbour; Washington Hotline; Mammograms, ovarian cancer with Representative DeLauro; From Missiles to Mammograms; PCN Profiles: US Senator Arlen Specter, July 24, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 38)
  - PCN Profiles: One Hour Interview by Bill Bova, July 24, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 39-40)
  - Floor Statement: Campaign Finance Independent Counsel, July 24, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 41)
  - Fox News Sunday: Interview with Senators Specter and Lieberman about Campaign Finance Abuses, July 27, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 42)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Terrorism, Technology and Government Information; Atlanta Olympic Bombing; with Director Freeh, July 28, 1997 (Box 1129, Video 43-44)
  - MSNBC, CBS Evening News: Independent Counsel and Campaign Finance; Report on Staffers Taking Trips to China, July 22, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 1)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee: Arlen Specter's Questioning, July 8-24, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 2)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Interview with Senators Specter and Lieberman on Campaign Finance Abuses, July 25, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 3)
  - Random Network Coverage: General Fogleman Retirement and Olympic Park Bombing, July 28, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 4)
  - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Technology, and Government Information: Atlanta Olympic Bombing, Louis Freeh and Mike Shaheen, July 28, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 5)
  - Fox News Sunday: Lieberman and Arlen Specter, July 29, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 6)
  - LTV Closing Segments: Pittsburgh Coverage, July 29, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 7)
  - Washington Hotline, July 29, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 8)
  - CNN Crossfire: Interview with Senators Specter and Durbin on Campaign Finance Abuses and Governmental Affairs Hearings, July 31, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 9-10)
  - Governmental Affairs Special Investigation, July 31, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 11-12)
  - Governmental Affairs Hearing with Torricelli; Campaign Finance Reform; CNN Inside Politics: Democracy for Sale - White House Tapes and Chinese Con., July 1997 (Box 1130, Video 13-14)
  - NET Direct Line with Paul Weyrich: Campaign Finance Hearings, July 1997 (Box 1130, Video 15)
  - NET Direct Line with Paul Weyrich; Newsclips of Ebonics Hearing, July 1997 (Box 1130, Video 16)
  - The Learning Channel: TWA Flight 800, One Year Later, July 1997 (Box 1130, Video 17-18)
  - News Segments: Olympic Park Bombing Clips, August 1, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 19)
  - NBC Meet the Press: Interview with Senators Specter and Lieberman about Campaign Abuses and Governmental Affairs Hearings, August 3, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 20)
  - WHP, WHTM: Children's Insurance in Harrisburg, August 6, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 21)
  - WGAL, WHP, WHTM Press Conference in Washington: Victims' Protection, August 6, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 22)
  - Senator Specter Plans: New Postal Facility, August 7, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 23)
  - WGAL-TV Children's Health; WPVI-TV Postal Facility News Stories, August 5 and 7, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 24)
  - Various Networks: UPS Strike and Line Item Veto, August 11, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 25)
  - WTXF: Senator Specter, Hearing on Judicial Nominee; Senator Specter, Bay Front Project (various), August 11, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 26)
  - NBC Nightly news: Interview with Huang; CNN Inside Politics with Representative Greenword; MSNBC: Ruby Ridge Bulletin, August 20, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 27)
  - WPXI, WTAE: Senator Specter, LTV Plant Closure/Saving Jobs; WPXI, WTAE: Senator Specter, Expanding Airport, August 20 and 22, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 28)
  - Senator Specter Discusses UPS Settlement, August 28, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 29)
  - Floor Action: Senator Specter LHHS, September 2, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 30)
  - Floor Statements: Various Subjects, September 2, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 31)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Government Affairs Hearings opposite Senator Torricelli about Campaign Finance Abuses and Governmental Affairs Hearings, September 3, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 32-33)
  - C-SPAN, Washington Journal: Governmental Affairs Hearings Opposite Senator Glenn about Campaign Finance Abuses, September 3, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 34-35)
  - CNN Crossfire: Interview with Senators Specter and Durbin about Governmental Affairs Hearings, September 4, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 36)
  - CNN Crossfire: PBS NewsHour: Specter Interview, September 4, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 37)
  - Education Subcommittee Hearing: Representative Bill Goodling, Secretary Riley, September 4, 1997 (Box 1130, Video 38)